



LU PEI-YUN CHUNG

UX, UI, and Product Designer

Working with consumer-focused product companies, SaaS, and b2b & b2c platforms, I have 3 years of working experience in UX, UI, 2 years of UX Researcher and Designer Consulting, besides 10+ years in Visual Design including 3D, Animation, and Video Editing. I specialize in HCI and GUI for websites and Apps.

EXPERIENCE

User Experience Researcher, Designer, and Data Analytics Consultant - Center for Digital Experiences at Pratt Institute, New York, USA

Sep 2019 to Present

Selected Clients: New York Cares, Sue Rock Originals, Archivists Round Table.

Overall services: Provide User Research, Digital Analytics, Usability Evaluation, and Experience Design.

- Aligned stakeholder expectations by defining goals/ scope, KPIs, and timeline.
- Leveraged insights from different qualitative and quantitative research methods to explore opportunities and confirm design solutions.
- Provide final deliverables in the form of formal reports, slides, and presentations, prototypes, or dashboards.

Feb 2019 to May 2019

Designer - Kronos Research Inc., Taiwan

Developed Career Site front-end, design, photography. Designed Virtual Currency Wallet MVP, Uls, prototypes.

Feb 2017 to Apr 2018

UX Designer - Shopline Inc., Taiwan

Designed Merchant App, conducting the usability test. Delivered UIs of POS (Point of Sale) system. Revamped the Admin platform and storefront website. Compiled design guidelines and design principles. Designed customized websites on desktop and mobile.

Oct 2016 to Dec 2016

UI Designer - Al Group Corp, Taiwan

In Charge front-end, web design, and App UIs design.

Feb 2016 to Aug 2016

UI Designer - Techgiant Art Tech Inc., Taiwan

Devised product brand design, tangible Uls, and VUls. Designed web design, graphic illustration, photography.

EDUCATION

Pratt Institute, New York, United States

Sep 2019 to Present

M.S. in Information Experience Design

GPA: 3.85/4.0, Full-Ride Merit Scholarship.

National Kaohsiung Normal University, Taiwan

Sep 2013 to Jun 2016 M.F.A. in Visual Design

Graduated Thesis Score: 92.0/100.0, 1 First place

Sep 2009 to Jun 2013 **B.Des. in Visual Design**

GPA: 3.91/4.0, 3 First places and 2 Second places.

SELECT SKILL

User flows, Wireframes, Prototypes, Motion Uls, App, Web Design, WCAG, VUIs, Emotional Design.

Five Ws, Scenarios, Personas, User Journey Map, Competitors Analysis, Card Sort, Tree Test, Site Map.

Interviews, Observations, Questionnaires, Heuristic Evaluations, Design Critique, Usability Testing.

Social Media Analytics, SEO Audit Report, Google Data Studio, Google Analytics, Google Spreadsheets.